{"data":[{"question":"Very ________ people knew about it.","a":"few","b":"less","c":"much","d":"little","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"He is a man of ________ words.","a":"less","b":"little","c":"fewer","d":"few","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A man of few words: means a man who doesn't talk much","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1927 Charlie Chaplin received a public ________ from Hollywood in the form of a special Oscar.","a":"apologize","b":"apologise","c":"apology","d":"apologizer","answer":"3","explain":"\n+ Noun phrase: (a\/an\/the )Adj + Noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"________ heard about the book, but ________ read it.","a":"Many \/ few","b":"Much \/ little","c":"Many \/ little","d":"Few \/ Fewer","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0\n- This case: many= many people, few= few people.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you know English? \"Just ________\"","a":"much","b":"many","c":"little","d":"less","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Do\/say\/know + little\/much....(not + few\/many..).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"She has very ________ knowledge of the matter.","a":"few","b":"little","c":"some","d":"many","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The forces were unequal, they were ________ we were ________.","a":"many \/ few","b":"much \/ little","c":"few \/ much","d":"little \/ much","answer":"1","explain":"\n - Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun (forces).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"We have imported ________ computers this year than last year.","a":"few","b":"less","c":"fewer","d":"many","answer":"3","explain":"\u00a0\n- We use the comparative form of short adverb (few)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"There has been ________ demand for computers this year than last year.","a":"few","b":"little","c":"fewer","d":"more","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adverb (much)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Always make sure your luggage has ________ on it when you travel.","a":"a card","b":"a cartel","c":"a label","d":"a traveling-bag","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Label: a piece of paper or another material that is attached to something and gives information about it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}